The incredible true story of an underdog who never gave up.
One Chance is a drama, comedy, music film directed by David Frankel.
This film follows the remarkable and inspirational true story of Paul Potts, a shy,
bullied shop assistant by day and an amateur opera singer by night.
Paul Potts, played by James Corden.
Julz, played by Alexandra Roach.
Yvonne, played by Julie Walters.
Roland Potts, played by Colm Meaney.
Hydrangea, played by Jemima Rooper.
Braddon, played by Mackenzie Crook.
One Chance is a 2013 British biographical film about opera singer and Britain's Got Talent
winner Paul Potts, directed by David Frankel and written by Justin Zackham.
It was screened in the Special Presentation section at the
2013 Toronto International Film Festival.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional.